Contact

contact@vaibhavchopra.codes

www.linkedin.com/in/ vaibhavchopra2001 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Full-Stack Development
Node.js
Python (Programming Language)

Honors-Awards

CodeVar'19 Finalist

Apptitude Hackathon Winner - 2nd Prize all over VIT-Vellore

Hack the Hourglass Hackathon Winner - 2nd prize all over India

Vaibhav Chopra

Full Stack Web Developer | Web Developer at PrishaPolicy, Core Committee Member at MSTC-VIT and ISTE-VIT

New Delhi

Summary

A full-stack developer with 2 years of experience in front-end, backend and python development. A communicative developer who specializes in object-oriented programming languages. A second-year Computer Science and Engineering student of Vellore Institute of Technology interested in web technologies and task automation.

Experience

PrishaPolicy
Web Developer
August 2020 - Present (2 months)
Delhi, India

Microsoft Student Technical Community — VIT Vellore Core Committee Member December 2019 - Present (10 months) Tamil Nadu, India

A Microsoft-backed community of passionate tech-enthusiasts which drives projects in various forthcoming domains that include Blockchain, Data Science, and many more with partners like Foxmula and MLH.

Indian Society for Technical Education
10 months

GraVITas Event Coordinator - Google Firebase
July 2020 - Present (3 months)

Tamil Nadu, India

Core Committee Member December 2019 - Present (10 months)

Vellore, Tamil Nadu, India

Indian Society for Technical Education or ISTE is a national, non-profit Society with an aim to assist and contribute to the production and development of top-quality professional engineers with partners like Adobe and JetBrains.

Applutions Softech Pvt Ltd ReactJS Developer June 2020 - September 2020 (4 months) India

Developed multiple React apps for projects.

IEEE Professional Communication Society, VIT Vellore Core Committee Member June 2020 - July 2020 (2 months)

Vellore, Tamil Nadu, India

thevitbud Full Stack Web Developer January 2020 - June 2020 (6 months) Delhi, India

Developed website and PWAs using HTML, CSS, Javascript on the front end and Google Firebase and NodeJS for a custom backend for the operations of the VITBud platform.

Education

Vellore Institute of Technology
Bachelor's degree, Computer Science and Engineering · (2019 - 2023)